《致命女人》前情提要
Previously on Why Women Kill.
防水的
It's waterproof.
那它不会被我喜悦的泪水弄坏了
So it's safe from my tears of joy.
怎么了  我让你丢人了吗
What's wrong? Am... am I embarrassing you?
-你至少收下花吧  -不行
- At least take the flowers. - No!
如果你连个小礼物都不收
If you won't accept this simple gift,
那我们的未来还有什么指望呢
then what does that say about our future?
我们没有未来
We have no future.
-汤米·哈特  -艾米
- Tommy Harte? - Amy?
我不知道你最近有没有交往对象
I don't know if you're seeing anyone these days,
不过我今晚很需要有人陪我给我打气
but I could really use some cheering up.
我本来是有对象的
I was... seeing someone.
但是她最近跟我分手了
But, uh, she recently broke up with me.
爱情总是要冒风险的
Love is always a risk.
爱的机会不是每天都有的
The chance for love doesn't come around every day.
你周五有空吗
Are you free Friday?
有的  爱人
Yes, lover.
还是叫夫人吧
"Ma'am" Will be fine.
既然洁德要和我们一起住
Now that Jade's gonna live with us,
我们就得找到介绍她的方式
we gotta have some way to introduce her.
为什么不说她是我们的家人呢
Well, why don't we just say she's family?
我喜欢这个
I love that.
洁德  出什么事了
Jade, what's going on?
-杜克要杀了茶缸  茶缸
- Duke is gonna kill Teacup. - Teacup?
是我们的狗  他说如果我不去见他
Our dog. He says if I don't meet with him,
他就要杀死它
he's gonna put her down.
过去两年里
For the last two years,
我一直都是那个连剧本都写不完的可悲伊莱
I've been pathetic Eli who... who can't finish a screenplay,
账单也付不起
who can't help pay the bills.
我只需要一场胜利
I just need a fucking win.
我只想让自己感觉像个爷们儿
I just want to feel like a man
把狗救下来  做得足够好
and save a dog and have that be good enough.
洁德
Jade!
艾普尔人很好
April is very sweet.
她非常自由随性
She's so free-spirited.
你不知道我们在一起有多开心
You wouldn't believe the fun we have together.
尝一块
Try one.
你懂的  大麻
You know, marijuana?
好像没什么感觉啊
I don't think it's working.
你看起来像喝醉了
You're acting like you're drunk.
那可能是因为飞叶子
That might be the pot.
-飞叶子  -就是大麻
- Pot? - It's marijuana.
我们晚点再谈这事
We will talk about this later.
我想做个歌手
I want to be a singer.
真的吗
Really?
有一天我会出人头地
I'm gonna be somebody someday.
致命女人
第一季  第五集
你长大后想当什么
我想当妈妈
I want to be a mommy.
我想当电影明星
I want to be a movie star.
我想当超级英雄
I want to be a superhero.
你每天会干什么
拯救世界
Saving the world.
照顾我的孩子
Taking care of my baby.
穿着高跟鞋参加派对
Going to parties in high heels.
用一个词形容你会爱上什么样的人
帅气
Handsome.
善良
Nice.
民主党人
Democrat.
如果你爱的人爱上了别人你会怎么办
什么
What?
这是玩笑吗
Is that a joke?
不可能的
That couldn't happen.
可如果发生了呢  你会怎么办
*我还是小女孩的时候*
* When I was just a little girl *
伯班克  1963年
*我问我妈妈*
* I asked my mother *
*我会成为什么*
* "What will I be? *
*我会变得漂亮吗  我会变得有钱吗*
* Will I be pretty, will I be rich?" *
*她这么对我说*
* Here's what she said to me *
*天意难违*
* Que será, será *
*该来的总会来*
* Whatever will be will be *
*我们无法预知未来*
* The future's not ours to see *
*天意难违*
* Que será, será *
*该来的总会来*
* What will be will be *
*天意难违*
* Que será, será. *
怎么样
So?
你觉得怎么样  波特先生
Um, what'd you think, Mr. Porter?
还行  孩子  还行
Not bad, kid. Not bad.
真的吗  这么说我得到这份工作了
Really? So I got the job?
就一晚  不过
It's just one night, but...
如果表现好的话  我们可以考虑让你长期驻扎
if it goes well, we could talk about something more permanent.
天呐  太谢谢你了
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
周二见
I'll see you Tuesday.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
艾普尔  你的第一个唱歌工作
Oh, April, your first singing gig.
答应我你会来看
Promise me you'll come.
-周二晚上吗  -嗯
- Tuesday night? - Mm-hmm.
我一定不会错过
I wouldn't miss it.
太好了
Wonderful.
你终于能见到罗伯了
And you'll finally get to meet Rob.
什么
What?
我跟他说我有机会
I told him that there was a chance
得到这份工作
that I could be booking this gig,
他已经同意要来了
and he already agreed to come.
我会安排你们坐一桌
I'll put you two at a table together.
这样你们就能互相了解了
That way you can get to know each other.
迫不及待
Can't wait.
你得帮我选衣服
You'll have to help me find something to wear.
我在考虑穿那件有金属片的蓝色裙子
I'm thinking maybe that blue dress with the sequins.
嗯  那件不错
Oh, yes, that's nice.
出什么事了吗
Is something wrong?
我刚想起来
Actually, I just remembered,
我莉狄娅姑妈周二要做手术
my aunt Lydia is getting an operation Tuesday.
-手术  -为了
- An operation? - Mm, to...
治疗她的拇滑液囊肿
fix her bunion.
我答应了要把她从医院接回来
I agreed to bring her home from the hospital
然后照顾她一整晚
and look after her. All night.
你能找别人去照顾她吗
Well, can you get someone else to look after her?
你不能错过我的表演
You can't miss my show.
我已经答应她了
I already promised.
是个很大的拇滑液囊肿
And it's... such a big bunion.
是跟罗伯有关吧
This is about Rob, isn't it?
什么
What?
承认吧
Just admit it.
你不想见他
You don't want to meet him
因为你不看好我和罗伯的关系
because you don't approve of Rob and I's relationship.
相信我  不是因为这个
Believe me, that is not the reason.
整夜营业
就跟你说吧  我们迷路了
I'm telling you, we're lost.
如果你在我们下高速的时候
Well, maybe if you'd asked for directions
记得问个路的话...
when we got off the highway...
如果你能选个近一点的汽车旅馆的话...
Maybe if you'd picked a motel closer than 30 miles away...
我猜我们应该从这左转吧
Oh, I think we go left here?
我们是在兜圈子
Oh, we're going in circles.
这是我们第三次路过那个醉汉了
This is the third time we've passed that wino.
太昏暗了我都看不清路标
Well, it's too dark to read the signs.
停下  我去问问那家酒水店
Oh, stop and I'll ask at the liquor store.
我们在派克街
We're on Pike Street.
给我看下地图
Show me the map.
阿苏萨警局
开走吧  孩子
Move along, kid.
抱歉  我们正准备离开
Sorry, we were just leaving.
站住  可人儿  你被抓了
Not you, sweet cheeks. You're busted.
-被抓了  为什么  -卖淫
- Busted? For what? - Soliciting.
你觉得我是个妓女吗
You think I'm a hooker?
拜托  我穿的可是YSL
For God's sake, I'm wearing Yves Saint Laurent.
我可没说你不算成功
I didn't say you weren't successful.
她是和我一起的  先生
Uh, she's with me, sir.
她只是去问个路
She was just asking directions
因为我们迷路了
because we got lost.
放松  孩子  我是在帮你
Relax, kid. I'm doing you a favor.
你不会想要把初夜献给一位老手的
You don't want your first time to be with a pro.
你胆敢信口雌黄
How dare you?
我可是有名的慈善家
I'm a well-known philanthropist.
我不需要知道你的专长
I don't need to know your specialty.
-跟我走  -什么
- Let's go. - What?
赶紧的
Come on.
慢着  先生  她真的是我女朋友
Hey! Seriously, sir, she's my girlfriend.
我不相信
I find that hard to believe.
给他看你的驾照
Well, show him your license.
如果我们是刚见面
If we just met,
我怎么会知道他叫汤米·哈特
how do I know his name is Tommy Harte
住在帕萨迪纳市
and that he lives in Pasadena
奥克赫斯特大道74号
at 74 Oakhurst Drive?
他的生日是3月10号
His birthday is March 10.
好吧
Okay.
如果你们是帕萨迪纳来的情侣
So, if you're a couple from Pasadena,
为什么要去阿苏萨的汽车旅馆
why are you going to a motel in Azusa?
我们这是婚外情
We are having an illicit affair.
我们开了30多英里是为了避免被
We've driven 30 miles to avoid being spotted
他妈妈  也就是我最好的朋友
by his mother, who is my best friend,
以及我的同性恋丈夫撞见
and my husband, who is gay.
不得不说  你们还挺有创意
Well, I got to give you points for creativity.
玩得开心  孩子
Have fun, kid.
伊莱  你能不能帮我遛下茶缸
Eli! Hey, can you walk Teacup for me?
我在帮泰勒打包行李
I'm helping Taylor pack for her trip.
-好的没问题  -谢了
- Yeah, sure. - Thanks.
还是要去弗雷斯诺  是吗
Still going to Fresno, huh?
我必须去  这个会议数月前都已经定好了
I have to. This conference has been on the books for months.
亲爱的  你公司的人知道我们被袭击了
Honey, the people at your firm know that we were attacked.
如果你取消的话  他们一定会理解的
I mean, they wouldn't blink if you opted out.
我懂  但是我已经告诉了我的姐妹们我要回去
I know, but I told my sisters I'm coming to town,
她们仍旧威胁说这个夏天要来看我们
and they're still threatening to visit this summer,
所以我们应该在她们来之前
so we kind of want to break the news
先挑明我们目前的居住情况
about our living situation before that happens.
你为何不发个信息给她们呢
Why don't you just shoot them a text?
我才不要短信告知我姐妹我处在一段三人关系中
I'm not gonna tell my sisters I'm in a throuple via text.
确保你告诉她们这是你的主意  而非我的
Yeah. Just make sure you tell them it was your idea, not mine.
-但这确实是你的主意  -没错
- But it was your idea. - Yeah,
但是你的姐姐们已经够恨我的了
but your sisters hate me enough as it is.
我们就没必要再火上浇油了
We don't need to throw any more gas on that fire.
你还没见过她们  但是她们糟透了
You haven't met them yet, but they're awful.
好的  茶缸
All right, Teacup.
我们走
Whoa, here we go.
-拉马尔  -原来你还记得我是谁啊
- Lamar. - Oh! You do know who I am.
我正纳闷呢
I was curious
因为你已经躲我好几周了
'cause you've been avoiding me for weeks.
没有没有  我...
No, no, no, no. I...
我正准备打给你呢  哥们
I-I was absolutely gonna call you back, man.
我只是...最近太忙了
I just... I've been incredibly busy.
忙到有空养狗啊
I see you had time to get a dog.
对了  忘记告诉你了
Oh, forgot to tell you.
你会喜欢这个消息的
You'll like this.
我终于试了下三P
Finally had that threesome.
我很想问这和养狗有什么关系
I would ask what one has to do with the other,
不过还是他妈的算了吧
but never the fuck mind.
-我的剧本呢  -剧本
- Where is my script? - Script?
你许诺我一个月前就该写好了的那个剧本呢
The one you promised would be done a month ago?
我和派拉蒙影业谈好了的那个
The one I talked up to Paramount.
他们当时都很兴奋  如今都气炸了
Got 'em all excited, and now they're pissed off
不知道剧本是什么情况
wondering what happened to it.
就快...快要写好了
Well, it-it's almost done.
我只是...在做最后的细微改动
I'm just... making a few final tweaks.
得了吧
Oh, please.
比这更陈词滥调的怕是只剩"要有光"了吧
The only line older than that is "Let there be light."
不  我没撒谎  听着  我向你保证...
No, I'm not lying. Look, I-I swear to you...
我向你保证  一周内我会把剧本交给你
I swear to you, I will have it to you in one week.
不行  你只有24个小时
No. You got 24 hours.
计时开始
Starting now.
别这样啊  哥们  我们本该是朋友的
Come on, man, we're supposed to be friends.
听着  我是你的朋友
Look, I am your friend.
换做是其他经纪人早就抛弃你了
Any other agent would have kicked your ass to the curb long ago.
好吧  没错  当然了
Okay, well, yeah, and of course,
我很感激有你挺我
I'm grateful that you stood by me,
但是拜托了...宽限到这周五
but please, I mean... Give me till Friday.
最后期限是明早10点15分
You got till 10:15 tomorrow.
快点改吧
Tweak fast.
你是在搞婚外情吗
Are you having an affair?
真的吗  卡尔  早餐前说这个
Really, Karl, before breakfast?
不  我今早听到你讲电话
No, I heard you on the phone this morning.
你在和某人争执
You were arguing with someone,
除非这人找到一个隐蔽的地点  不然你拒绝见面
refusing to meet unless they found a discreet location.
你竟敢偷听私人谈话
You listened to a private conversation?
-你应该感到惭愧  -我确实很惭愧...
- You should be ashamed of yourself. - Well, I am...
在小巷子里和一个餐厅勤杂工做完爱之后
after I've had sex with a busboy in an alleyway,
但是偷听我心安理得
but I-I don't really break a sweat over eavesdropping.
无论如何  我不欠你什么解释
Regardless, I don't owe you any explanations,
-所以换个话题吧  -得了吧
- so drop the subject. - Oh, go on.
告诉我这人是谁
Tell me who it is.
是我们乡村俱乐部的朋友吗
Is it one of our friends from the country club?
网球教...不对  是那个厨子
The tennis instruct... No, the chef.
卡尔  我看你是嫉妒了吧
Karl, I believe you're jealous.
别傻了
Oh, don't be daft.
对了  如果他是一名叫朱利欧的餐厅勤杂工
Oh, by the way, if it is a busboy named Julio,
你能否替我向他问个好呢
will you give him my regards?
这讽刺可真是太美味了
Mm, the irony is just delicious.
是我们的某位邻居吗
Is it one of our neighbors?
随便你怎么猜  卡尔
Dig all you like, Karl.
就算我有婚外情
Even if I were having an affair,
你绝不会从我这里听到他的名字的
you'd never hear his name from me.
我们得谈谈汤米
We need to talk about Tommy.
坏消息是他最近一直鬼鬼祟祟的
The bed news is he's been acting strangely.
他整晚整晚的不在家
He leaves the house at all hours of the night.
回家后也不告诉我他去了哪里
Won't tell me where he's been when he comes home.
我希望汤米没有误入歧途
Oh, I do hope Tommy hasn't fallen in with the wrong crowd.
你为什么看着我
Why are you looking at me?
-我在递给你曲奇  -这样啊
- I'm offering you a cookie. - Oh.
好吧
Right.
好消息是我给他找了份新工作
The good news is I got him a new job
贝德尔的苗圃公司
working for Bader's Nursery.
他将去做入户照料
He'll be doing home care.
-入户照料  -也就是说他会去到别人家里
- Home care? - That means he'll go into people's houses
在他们外出工作或者度假时
and water their plants while they're at work
给植物浇浇水
or on vacation.
是吗
Will he?
这就是我来拜托你们的原因
This is where the favor comes in.
我要请我所有的朋友都雇佣汤米
I'm asking all of my friends to hire Tommy.
我得让他忙起来
I need to keep him busy.
先让我搞清楚  大家不在的时候
Just so I'm clear, people leave town
把家门钥匙给汤米
and give Tommy the keys to their homes?
我知道你在想什么  但是汤米
I know what you're thinking, but Tommy is
很值得信赖  他动作也很快
very trustworthy... and quick, too.
他会快进快出的
He'd be in and out.
我相信他一定会待到把工作"做完"才离开
I'm sure he'd stay long enough to get the job done.
那是当然
Of course.
我能把你们家算进去吗
Can I count you in?
何乐而不为呢
Oh, why not?
我们都很喜欢汤米  不是吗  亲爱的
We like Tommy, don't we, darling?
没错
Oh, yes.
我们当然喜欢他了
We certainly do.
可怜的艾普尔
Poor April.
如果你能看到她那副面庞
If you could have seen her face.
你不会想要让我接近淫妇那张脸的
Oh, you don't want me anywhere near that tramp's face
因为我会扇死她
because I will slap it.
今晚对她很重要
It's her big night.
她很想让我去  我深感荣幸
I was honored she wanted me to come so badly.
她就没其他朋友了吗
Doesn't she have any other friends?
还是说她也睡了她们的丈夫们
Or did she sleep with their husbands, too?
我很欣慰罗伯会去
I'm glad Rob is going.
她需要有人在那里鼓励她
She needs someone there to cheer her on.
我不明白
I don't get it.
这是场战争
This is war.
你正在跟另一个女人
You are fighting with another woman
争夺你的丈夫  而你快输了
over your husband and you are losing.
亲爱的
Honey!
他回来得真早  我在里面  罗伯
He's home early. I'm in here, Rob.
如果他告诉你  他周二得加班到很晚
If he tells you that he's got to work late Tuesday,
我就立刻吐一地
I will vomit and you will have to mop
你就得重新拖一遍地板
this floor up all over again.
你在这呢  你猜怎么着
There you are. Guess what?
我有好消息
I have amazing news.
是吗
You do?
我有两张世界职棒大赛的票
I got two tickets to the World Series.
什么时候的
For when?
我来猜猜看  周二吗
Let me guess. Tuesday?
还真的是周二
As a matter of fact, yeah.
是我老板送给我的
My boss gave them to me as a gift,
座位就在本垒后面
and they are right behind home plate.
你打算带谁去
Who are you taking?
这还用问吗
What do you mean, who am I taking?
当然是带我心爱的女孩
Only my best girl.
让我看看票
Let me see those.
我操
Holy crap!
他有两张世界职棒大赛的票
He's got two tickets to the World Series.
我刚才不是说了吗
Isn't that what I just said?
是周二的票吗
And these are for Tuesday?
对
Yeah.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我就想确认一下
Well, I just want to make sure
我们有没有忘了
we haven't forgotten about any plans
之前给周二定下的什么安排
we might have made for Tuesday?
不管之前安排了什么  都通通取消
Well, whatever plans we made, consider them canceled.
我和我的娇妻  以及道奇队和洋基队有个约会
I've got a date with my wife, the Dodgers and the Yankees.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了  你为什么不高兴
What's going on here? Why aren't you happy?
她可高兴了
Oh, she is very happy.
她只是不习惯你突然这么好
She's just not used to you being so wonderful.
罗伯  麻烦你先出去  我们还没拖完地
Rob, give us a second. We're not through with the mopping.
我得打给卡尔
I got to call Carl.
他会嫉妒得发狂
He's gonna be so jealous.
艾普尔会心碎的
April is going to be heartbroken.
谁管艾普尔死活啊
To hell with April.
你得着眼于大局
You've got to focus on the big picture.
他在你和她之间选了你
He's choosing you over her.
你要赢了
You're winning.
看来是的
I guess I am.
泰勒打来过
Hey. Taylor called.
她到弗雷斯诺了
Her plane landed in Fresno.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
自杀
Killing myself.
-用芝士吗  -没错
- With cheese? - Yeah. My plan is
我的计划就是吃到爆肥  然后死于高血压
to get super fat and then die of hypertension.
那得花好一段时间
That might take a while.
只有伟大的作家才有资格迅速死掉
Only great writers deserve quick deaths.
海明威  沃尔夫  普拉斯
Hemingway, Wolfe, Plath.
而我  我是个无才的作家
Me? I'm a bad writer,
我只配慢慢受折磨而死
so I deserve to die slowly,
充满痛苦  充满厌恶
painfully... disgustingly.
家里有黄芥末吗
Do we have any mustard?
没有
No.
但我们有蛋黄酱
But we have mayonnaise.
调味品中的战斗机
Oh, yes, the condiment of hacks.
拿过来
Bring it to me.
怎么了
What's going on?
如果我明早不能把剧本给他
My agent's gonna drop me
我的经纪人就要炒了我
if I don't get him my script by tomorrow morning.
你还没写完吗
And you're not finished?
我已经写了50页了  但是很糟糕
I-I've written 50 pages. Each just worst than the last.
别这么说
I doubt that.
我是说我还没写第三幕
I mean, I have no third act.
我就坐在这
I keep sitting here,
盯着我那唯一大火电影的海报
staring at the poster of my one and only hit,
《昨日珍妮》
祈祷有灵感到来
praying for some sort of inspiration.
看得越久我越明白
And the longer I look at it, the more I realize...
那只是昙花一现
it was a fluke.
我是说  出色的导演  一流的演员
I mean, brilliant director, stellar cast,
把我写的废话变成金子
all turning my crap dialogue into gold.
我该怎么告诉泰勒
How am I gonna tell Taylor
我失去了我的经纪人
that I lost my fucking agent?
把那50页给我
Give me the 50 pages.
干嘛  你要用来打我吗
Why, so you can beat me with them?
我觉得我能给你一些真诚的建议
Because I think it might help you to get some honest feedback.
你懂写作吗
Do you know anything about writing?
我知道我喜欢什么
I know what I like.
如果我觉得你的剧本写得不错
And if I think that your script's in decent shape,
你就有信心把它写完了
you'll have the confidence to finish the damn thing.
好吧  如果这50页只是我写的屁话呢
Yeah, and what if it's just 50 pages of me shitting the bed?
那么我就去商店给你买
Then I will go to the store and I will buy you
所有人类已知的奶酪
every kind of cheese known to man.
还有蛋黄酱
And mayonnaise.
我需要吃很多蛋黄酱
Gonna need lots of mayonnaise.
罗伯  你在干嘛  我们要迟到了
Rob, what are you doing? We're going to be late.
我在找我的旧棒球手套
I'm looking for my old baseball glove.
也许我能让桑迪·科法斯在上面签名
Maybe I can get Sandy Koufax to sign it.
今晚别打扰科法斯先生了  他要工作
Don't bother Mr. Koufax tonight. He'll be working.
签个名的时间还是有的
Eh, he can sign one glove.
也许是在车库的某个箱子里
Maybe it's in one of the boxes in the garage.
不  应该在这里面的
No, it should be in this one.
斯坦顿家
Stanton residence.
等等
Hold on.
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right about the garage.
去找下工具屉旁的盒子  我得接个电话
Check the box by the tool drawer. I got to take this.
是谁
Who is it?
一个同事  我马上下来
Uh, a guy from work. Uh, I'll be right down.
你他妈以为你在干嘛
What the hell do you think you're doing?
我说了不能打电话到我家
I said never to call me here.
我已经告诉你了我和我妻子有事
I already told you, I got plans with my wife.
她要我带她出去吃饭
She's making me take her out to dinner.
别哭  听着  我讨厌你哭
Don't cry. L-Look, I hate it when you cry.
这事我一点办法没有
There's nothing I can do about this.
我得挂了
Now-now I got to go.
好吧  你是对的
Well, you were right about the garage.
没找到你的手套
No sign of your glove.
没事  我们走吧
Eh, it doesn't matter. Let's get going
不然我们会错过国歌演奏的
or we'll miss the national anthem.
宝贝  我觉得我去不了了
Honey, I don't think I can go.
什么
What?
我感觉不舒服
I'm not feeling well.
你看着没事啊
You look fine to me.
罗伯特
Robert.
你记得我们在新墨西哥的旅行吗
You remember our trip to New Mexico?
你是说  你得...
You mean, you got...
对  我得待在洗手间附近
Yes. I should stay close to a bathroom.
好吧  体育场里有洗手间
Well, they got bathrooms at the stadium.
在陌生人面前我做不到
I could never do that to total strangers.
想要我在家陪你吗
Want me to stay home with you?
别傻了
Don't be silly.
真好  谢天谢地  因为我真的很想去
Oh, good. Thank God, 'cause I really want to go.
再见
Bye.
艾普尔  我是希拉
April, it's Sheila.
我姑妈没事
My aunt is fine.
我可以去听你唱歌了
I can come hear you sing after all.
对  我也很开心
Yes. I'm happy, too.
真开心见到你们
It is so good to see you guys.
真希望妈妈也能来
I just wish Mama could've made it.
她怎么样了
How is she?
-讨厌依旧  -还是那么刻薄
- Nasty as ever. - Mean as the day is long.
我们为了她拼命工作
We work our fingers to the bone for that woman.
但那永远不够
But it's never good enough for her.
医生说她能活到一百岁
The doctor says she could live to be 100.
她会的  就是为了刁难我们
And she'll do it, just to spite us.
好吧  听着  我知道她很难照顾
Well, look, I know she can be difficult to care for,
我真希望我能帮上忙
and I wish I could help out more.
别担心  宝贝
Oh, don't worry about it, sugar.
-我们不恨你  -反正不是特别恨
- We don't resent you. - Not much, anyway.
如果你能偶尔把她接到你家住的话
Would be nice if you could take her off our hands
那就再好不过了
every now and then.
你那大房子里有多余的房间吗
Got an extra room in that big house of yours?
不用太高档
Don't need to be fancy.
地下室也行
Oh, it could be the cellar for all we care.
我很愿意帮忙  但是有点棘手
I would really like to help out, but it would be tricky,
考虑到我现在的居家状况
given my current living situation.
好吧  我本想一开始就和你们说的
Okay, I meant to lead with this when I sat down,
但是真相是
but the truth is...
我的婚姻不再开放了
I am no longer in an open marriage.
-你离开伊莱了  -谢天谢地
- You left Eli? - Thank you, Jesus.
没有  我没有离开伊莱
No, I didn't leave Eli,
我让我的炮友住进了我们家
I moved my lover into our home.
我们三个正式在一起了
The three of us are officially a throuple.
这事可以告诉妈妈吗
Would it be okay if we tell Mama?
这肯定能气死她
'Cause this will kill her.
希拉
Sheila.
-你好  -看看你
- Hi. - Look at you.
-你真漂亮  -谢谢
- You're lovely. - Thanks.
我好紧张
Oh, I'm so nervous.
没事的
You're going to be great.
孩子  再过10分钟就该你了
Hey, kid, you're on in ten.
谢谢你  波特先生
Oh, thank you, Mr. Porter.
你在看什么
What are you looking for?
说来挺傻的  罗伯说他不能来了
It's silly. Rob told me he can't make it.
我  我总觉得他也许会给我个惊喜
I just... I keep thinking maybe he'll surprise me.
宝贝  你现在不能想这个
Honey, you can't worry about that right now.
你马上就要表演了
You've got a show to do.
你说得没错  感谢你能来这里看我表演
You're right. Thank you so much for being here.
惊艳全场吧
Knock 'em dead.
好的
Okay.
*我还是小女孩的时候*
* When I was just a little girl *
*我问我妈妈  我会成为什么*
* I asked my mother, What will I be? *
*我会变得漂亮吗  我会变得有钱吗*
* Will I be pretty, will I be rich? *
*她这么对我说*
* Here's what she said to me *
*天意难违*
* Que será, será *
*该来的总会来*
* Whatever will be, will be *
*我们无法预知未来*
* The future's not ours to see *
*天意难违*
* Que será, será *
*该来的总会来*
* What will be, will be... *
怎样
Well?
很好
It's good.
你不喜欢
You hate it.
不  很好
No. It's good.
-不算出色  -部分出色
- It's not great. - Some of it's great.
对话  餐厅里的戏
The dialogue, the scenes in the diner...
直接说哪里不好吧
Just-just skip to what sucks.
就是你的主人公
That would be your lead character.
伊娃怎么了
What's wrong with Eva?
她差不多等了15页的篇幅  就希望男人来拯救她
She waits around for 15 pages hoping a man will save her.
她是个受害者  我讨厌受害者
She's a victim. I hate victims.
是啊  好吧  让她更主动一点当然可以
Yeah, yeah. Okay. I mean, make her more proactive, sure.
她不能做点有趣的事情
And can't she do something interesting
让自己免除麻烦事吗
to get out of trouble?
-什么叫有趣的事情  -比如第40页
- What do you mean, interesting? - Like, on page 40,
她被男人抛弃在餐厅里  心碎不已  对吗
she's abandoned at the diner and totally broke, right?
-是啊  -那你让她
- Yeah. - So, let her
偷走店主的卡车
steal the owner's truck
然后开到毒贩子那里去放一把火
and then she drives to the drug dealer's house and starts a fire.
等毒贩子从前门跑出来的时候
And when he runs out the front,
她从后门进去  把她被他夺走的钱全都拿回来
she goes in the back and gets the money that he took from her.
还有他的枪
And his gun.
绝对得拿走他的枪
She'd definitely take his gun.
我是说
Wow. Um, I mean,
这样绝对显得她更积极主动了
I-it's definitely more proactive.
只是...我不知道  我没这样想过伊娃
It's just... I don't know, I-I never saw Eva that way.
我是说  她是个好女孩
I mean, she's... she's a nice girl.
是啊  但好女孩也都会犯法
Yeah, but nice girls, they break the law every day.
只要有需要
When they need to.
好吧  行了  我知道你的意见了
Okay. All right, I hear you.
应该让伊娃并不像表面看上去这样
There's more to Eva than meets the eye.
没错
Exactly.
好了  开始吧  打开电脑去工作
So now, get started, open your laptop, get to work.
你还有22个小时
You have 22 hours.
不过你怎么会想到这种设定呢
How did you come up with that stuff, anyway?
或许我也并不像表面看起来这样
Maybe there's more to me than meets the eye.
嗨  抱歉我来晚了
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
没关系  你明白要做什么了吗
It's okay. Are you clear on what to do?
我想是的
I guess.
我们真的确定吗  如果被抓住的话
Are we sure about this? I mean, if we get caught...
没错  这样非常冒险
Yes. It's very risky.
我想聪明的做法是我们两个结束外遇
I suppose the smart thing to do is end this affair
再也不发生关系
and never have sex again.
好吧
Fine.
我不知道为什么会觉得杜博纳太太的床这么舒适
I don't know why Mrs. Dubner's bed feels amazing.
因为床单好  都是埃及棉
It's the sheets. They're Egyptian cotton.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我在我爸洗衣店工作的时候
I used to wash sheets like this
经常洗这样的床单
when I worked in my father's laundry.
你爸爸是开洗衣店的
Your dad owned a laundry?
你以为我一直是富人家的孩子吗
You think I was born rich?
是的
Well... yeah.
才不是呢
Not even close.
我12岁的时候  非常羡慕这奢华的一切
When I was 12, I used to covet things like this.
我有一次悄悄拿了有污渍的床单回家
Once, I took some satin sheets home.
我想知道那种床单的触感
I wanted to see what it felt like
睡上去的感觉  哪怕只有一晚
to sleep on them, just for one night.
我妈妈发现了  她非常生气
My mother caught me. She was so angry.
她命令我立刻洗好并熨好了它们
She made me wash and iron them right there.
那可是凌晨2点啊
It was 2:00 in the morning.
然后她就把床单拿走了
And then she took them away.
真可惜
That's a shame.
我妈说  如果你想睡贵的床单
Mother said, "If you want to sleep on expensive sheets,
那就好好挑一挑枕边人
choose wisely who you sleep next to."
所以她基本就是要你嫁给有钱人
So, uh, she basically told you to marry for money.
这个可真不是什么好建议
That's, uh, some really bad advice.
我这样做了两次
Well, I followed it twice.
在遇到卡尔之前  我不觉得自己能为爱结婚
I didn't think of marrying for love until Karl.
我之前从没跟人讲过这事
I never told that story before.
给任何人听
To anyone.
谢谢你先告诉了我
Thanks for telling me first.
如果你真的想谢我
If you really want to thank me,
就过来这里
get over here.
我感觉很糟糕
Oh, I feel so badly about this.
让你费了这么大劲
After you went to all the trouble
载我从机场回来
of taking me to the airport.
没关系  乔伊斯
It's fine, Joyce.
你生病的时候  没有人会非要强迫你搭乘飞机的
Nobody expects you to get on a plane when you're feeling ill.
是苗圃店的车
Oh, it's the plant van.
汤米肯定在
Tommy must be here.
最终我跟伊莱坦白了
So, finally, I confessed to Eli
洁德对我的重要性
how much Jade meant to me,
他也同意让她一直跟我们住在一起
and he agreed to let her live with us, permanently.
我知道这种方式很不传统
Yes, I know, it's unconventional,
你们可能会不赞同
and you probably don't approve,
但是我们相处得很融洽
but... it's working.
只要你们高兴就好
Well, as long as you're happy.
那才是最重要的
That's what matters.
真的吗
Really?
你们就只想说这些吗
That's all you have to say?
既然你这么问  我问一个问题
Since you asked, I have a question.
-来了  -你还爱着伊莱吗
- Here we go. - Do you still love Eli?
-当然  -而你还爱着这个女人
- Of course. - And you also love this woman?
是的  我很好奇他们之间是什么感觉
Yes. I'm wondering, how do they feel about each other?
这个嘛...
Oh. Well...
我就知道她还没有想过这件事
I knew she hadn't thought it through.
-根本没想过  -没错
- Hadn't even crossed her mind. - Mm-hmm.
等等  伊莱和洁德也喜欢彼此
Hold on. Eli and Jade like each other.
那不是问题
That's not a problem.
现在还不是  万一他比你更喜欢她了呢
Not yet. What happens when he likes her more than you?
等她受够了跟别人分享爱人呢
What happens when she gets tired of sharing?
-那你怎么办  女士  -变成局外人
- Where does that leave you, missy? - On the outside
眼睁睁看着他们在一起
looking in, that's where.
才不会发生这种事
That's not gonna happen.
绝对不会
It's not.
显然我们不了解洁德
Obviously, we don't know Jade.
所以没法判断她
So we can't judge her.
但我们了解伊莱
But we know Eli.
我们亲眼见过他让你受的苦
We saw what he put you through.
没错  我们经历过一段阴暗时期
Yes, we went through a dark time,
但那是两年前的事了
but that was two years ago.
"阴暗时期"  那家伙可是个瘾君子
"A dark time"? The man's a drug addict.
你们一半的积蓄都被他拿去买毒品了
Half your savings went up his nose.
那人根本没有自控能力
The man's incapable of self-control.
现在他床上还有另一个女人
And now he's got another woman in his bed?
你以为会发生什么
The hell did you think was gonna happen?
够了
Stop it!
我知道你们想激怒我
I know you're trying to bait me,
但没用的
but it's not gonna work.
我告诉你们  伊莱变了
I'm telling you, Eli has changed.
天真的妹妹  男人死性不改的
Oh, baby sister, men never change.
他们只是越来越会隐瞒
They just get better at keeping secrets.
有人吗
Hello?
我是杜博纳太太
It's Mrs. Dubner.
你不是说她要去法国吗
You said she was going to France.
是啊  我妈今早还送她去机场
Yeah, my mom took her to the airport this morning.
汤米  你在哪
Tommy, where are you?
你得躲起来
You have to hide!
把床铺好
Make the bed.
我没法同时做这两件事
I can't do both.
我知道你觉得我疑病症很严重
I know you think I'm a ridiculous hypochondriac,
但我是真的很疼
but the pain is real.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
你只需回房躺下休息
You just need to lie down in your room.
杜博纳太太  你没赶上飞机吗
Mrs. Dubner. Did you miss your flight?
我偏头疼  我需要休息
I'm having a migraine. I need to rest.
不  你不能进去
No, uh... you can't go in there.
为什么
Why not?
我刚刚喷了东西
I, uh, just sprayed.
什么东西
Sprayed?
杀虫剂
Uh, insecticide.
你的榕树上有只白粉虱
Your, uh, your ficus had a white fly.
-我从没见过有什么白粉虱  -它们...
- I've never seen any white fly. - Yeah, well, they're...
它们个头很小的  瞧
they're pretty tiny... see?
天呐  快弄死它
Oh, my God. Kill it!
我不知道你这么快就回来了
See, I-I didn't know that you would be back so soon,
所以我用了很浓的杀虫剂
so I used a very strong insecticide.
你偏头疼还吸入那些臭气的话...
You inhale those fumes with a migraine and...
你说得对  我能闻到
You're right. I can smell it.
对  你最好待在楼下吧
Yeah, y-you better stay downstairs.
别傻站着  来扶她下楼
Don't just stand there, help her down.
你得赶紧去一趟药房
We need you to run to the pharmacy.
现在吗
Now?
我的药吃完了  这是我的处方
I'm out of medication. Here's my prescription.
我得去打开卧室的窗户
I should go open some windows in the bedroom.
散散臭味儿
To air it out.
快点
Oh, hurry.
乔伊斯很难受
Joyce is in agony.
乔伊斯不舒服  我得去药房
Joyce is sick. I have to go to the drugstore.
我要怎么离开这里
Well, how am I supposed to get out of here?
我不知道
I don't know.
-喂  -卡尔  是我  需要你帮个忙
- Hello? - Karl, it's me. I need your help.
大声点  我听不清
Speak up, I can hardly hear you.
我被困在乔伊斯·杜博纳家里
I'm trapped in Joyce Dubner's house.
老天  她是不是又叨逼她切阑尾那破事了
Oh, dear, is she telling her appendectomy story again?
她不知道我在这  娜奥米也不知道
She doesn't know I'm here, and neither does Naomi.
什么  娜奥米也在那里
Sorry, Naomi's there?
没错  我被困在楼上了
Yes, and I'm trapped upstairs.
楼上
Upstairs?
这是不是跟你没在发生的婚外情有关
Would this have anything to do with the affair you're not having?
现在不是说这个的时候
Now is not the time!
你语气好恶劣哦  我要挂电话了
Oh, what a nasty tone. I think I'm gonna hang up.
好吧  好吧  行
All right, all right, fine, fine.
我是在搞婚外情
I'm having an affair.
现在能不能拜托你过来
Now can you please come over here
引开她们注意  好让我溜出去
and create a distraction so I can get out?
这是当老公应该做的
What are husbands for?
伊莱
Eli?
Hey, Eli.
醒醒  伊莱
Eli, hey.
你睡着了
You fell asleep.
-天呐  几点了  -凌晨4点
- Oh, my God, what time is it? - It's 4:00 in the morning.
什么  惨了
What? Oh, shit.
-你写完多少了  -61页
- How much have you done? - 61 pages.
好消息是这故事的方向对了
The good news is that I think the story's working,
但我说不好  我分辨不出来
but, I mean, I don't know, I can't tell,
因为我实在太累了  无法思考
'cause I'm just so tired I can't even think.
你必须继续写
Well, you have to keep going.
-拉马尔早餐前就要收到剧本  -我知道
- Lamar expects the script by breakfast. - I know, I know.
我已经连续写了10小时了
I've been writing for ten hours straight.
相信我  我汽油里已经一滴油箱都没有了
Believe me when I tell you that there is no tank left in the gas.
等等  不  我没说错
Wait. No, that's right.
等等  我有东西能帮你
Hold on, I have something.
找到了
Here we go.
吃掉它
Take this.
这是什么
What is that?
我开了药治疗我的注意力不集中症
I get pills to help with my ADHD.
这药能帮你提神和集中注意力
They give you a lift and they help you focus.
我觉得我不应该吃
I don't think I should.
没事的  这没什么大不了
It's fine. It's not a big deal.
大学生们期中考前经常吃
Like, college kids take them all the time
用来临时抱佛脚
to cram for midterms and shit.
还是不了  谢谢你
Yeah... No, thank you.
好吧  你自己决定
Okay, it's your choice.
-不管了  把药给我  -你确定吗
- Fuck it, give me the pill. - Are you sure?
确定  我必须写完剧本
Yes, yes. I need to finish the script.
伊莱  你怎么来了
Eli. What are you doing here?
亲手把剧本交给你
Hand-delivering you my script.
你不能用邮件发给我吗
You couldn't send it by e-mail?
不  不行  因为我需要
No, no, no, I could not, because I needed
直视你双眼  然后告诉你
to look you in the eye when I told you
我没写完
that it's not done.
-你不是吧  -可是
- Oh, come on... - But, but,
我写了八十页  而且很精彩
I finished 80 pages, and it's great.
精彩到你看后会打给我
So great that you're gonna call me,
为你有动过不再雇我的念头
and you're going to apologize for ever considering
而向我道歉
dropping me as a client.
你会说  "伊莱  你写得太好了
You're gonna say, "Eli, this is fucking brilliant.
我都等不及想看到结局了"
"I can't fucking wait to see how it ends.
你  我的朋友  真是个才华横溢的天才
You, my friend, are one fucking talented motherfucker."
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
我刚没看到你
I didn't see you there.
我现在要关门了
I'm shutting the door now.
好的
As well you should.
我找到你的眼罩了
I found your sleep mask.
拿过来  这里太亮了
Bring it here. There's too much light.
什么声音
What the hell was that?!
有人刚撞到了我的车
Somebody just rammed into my car.
卡尔
Karl?
-你都干了些什么  -很抱歉
- What have you done? - I'm so sorry.
我为了躲一只猫猛打了方向盘
I-I swerved to avoid a kitten.
这不是乔伊斯·杜博纳家吗
Isn't this Joyce Dubner's house?
是的
Yes.
那乔伊斯在哪
So, where-where's Joyce?
娜奥米  你这么快就回来了
Naomi? You're back quickly.
外面出了什么事
What happened out there?
娜奥米
Naomi?
你一定是被烟呛到了
Oh, you must be inhaling fumes.
你最好喝点水
You better get some water.
这是怎么了
What happened here?
我刚从机场接了乔伊斯回家
I just brought Joyce home from the airport.
她病了  还有你丈夫刚撞上了我的车
She's ill, and your husband just crashed into my car.
是的  我当时在开车
Yes, and I was out for a drive
为了不撞上一只小狗不得不急打了方向盘
and had to swerve to avoid hitting a puppy.
你不是说是小猫吗
I thought it was a kitten.
反正是一只有毛的跑得很快的东西
Well, it had fur and moved quickly.
总之  撞车了
Anyway, crash.
太好了  汤米回来了
Oh, good, Tommy's back.
回来了
Back?
他刚在这给乔伊斯卧室的植物浇水
Well, he was here spraying the plants in Joyce's bedroom,
然后我让他去药店给她买药
and I sent him to the drugstore for her pills.
还真是巧啊  亲爱的
Well, wasn't that lucky, dear?
汤米刚好在卧室
Seems Tommy was right there in the bedroom
正派上用场
ready to be useful.
回家见  卡尔
Well, I'll see you at home, Karl.
我要去继续跑步了
I have to finish my jog.
是吗  亲爱的
Do you, darling?
因为我很肯定你已经跑完了[事情败露]
'Cause I'm pretty sure the jog is up.
我不理解你为什么不开心
I can't understand why you're not happy.
今晚很成功
Tonight was a triumph.
你应该在街上起舞
You should be dancing in the street.
是的  我知道
Yeah. I know.
可能是我真的希望罗伯能来
Guess I just really hoped Rob would show up.
亲爱的  会好起来的
Sweetie, it's going to be okay.
不  不会的
No, it's not.
再也不会好了
It's not going to be okay ever again.
为什么
Well, why not?
因为我爱上他了
Because I'm falling in love with him.
伊莱
Eli?
发生什么了
What's going on?
拉马尔刚打给我了
I just got a call from Lamar.
好吧  他说了什么
Okay. What did he say?
他说这是我写过的最好的剧本
He said it's the best thing I've ever written.
-真的吗  -是的  他说我写得很有智慧
- Really? - Yeah. He said it's smart
而且很刺激  还有伊娃那个角色
and exciting and that the character of Eva
很"五味杂陈"
is "Deliciously complex."
然后他要我不要烂尾  但是...
And then he told me to not fuck up the ending, but, I mean,
重点是  他很喜欢
the point is, he loved it.
-我为你高兴  -天呐
- I'm so happy for you. - Oh, my God.
我该怎么谢谢你
How do I even begin to say thank you?
我没做什么
I didn't do much.
你有  你知道的
Yes, you did. You know you did.
如果我真的擅长写作的话
And if I was actually good at what I do,
我应该想出比"谢谢你"更好的辞藻
I would come up with something better than just "Thank you,"
但现在
but for now,
我只能想到这句话了  所以谢谢你
that's all I got, so thank you.
不  我接受
No, look, I'll take it,
-我接受  -谢谢你  谢谢你
- I'll take it. Oh. - Thank you, thank you.
恭喜
Congrats.
泰勒不在我们可以这样吗
A-Are we allowed to do this without Taylor?
我不确定
I'm not... not sure.
你觉得我很傻吧
You think I'm stupid, don't you?
我绝不会这么说
I would never say that.
这不在计划当中
Now this was not the plan.
我不应该这么在意他
I was not supposed to care this much.
他今晚没出现
When he didn't show up tonight,
让我顿悟
it just... hit me.
我现在该怎么办
What am I gonna do now?
我有种预感他在家
I have a hunch he's happier at home
远比在你面前表现得幸福
than he's led you to believe.
也就是说他会继续让你失望
Which means he'll continue to disappoint you.
你现在不需要那些
You don't need that right now.
你的事业终于开始有了起色
Your career is finally taking off.
你应该享受这段时光
You should be enjoying this time,
而不是为别的女人的丈夫神魂颠倒
not mooning over some other woman's husband.
要是他和她在一起那么幸福
I mean, why would he even be with me
为什么还要跟我在一起
if he was so happy with her?
或许她做了什么伤害他
Maybe she did something to hurt him
他需要时间去忘记她
and he needs time to forgive her.
我不是很理解
I don't really understand that.
很晚了  我该走了
It's late. I should go.
你该好好睡上一觉
And you should get some sleep.
希拉
Sheila.
你真是个贴心的朋友
You are such a good friend.
我觉得或许你是我有史以来最好的朋友了
I think you're maybe the best I've ever had.
你今晚真的很出色
You really were wonderful tonight.
我要借用下你的卫生间
I need to use your bathroom.
里面很乱
Oh, uh, it's a mess.
我可以先整理下吗
Can I just clean up first?
不了
No!
你没事吧
Is everything okay?
我可能要在里面待一会了
Um, I... I may be in here a while.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
罗伯  你好  你怎么来了
Rob. Hi... What are you, what are you doing here?
我想知道你的演出怎么样了
I wanted to come hear about your show.
很顺利
Oh, it went great.
那就好
Oh, good.
我们应该庆祝下
Mm, we should celebrate.
我不行  我朋友在这儿
Oh, I can't. My friend is here.
我没看到人呢
I don't see anybody.
她在厕所
She's in the bathroom.
她怎么了
What's wrong with her?
她好像腹泻
I think she has diarrhea.
最近腹泻的人很多
Lot of that going around.
过来
Come here.
我们能明天再谈吗
Can we talk tomorrow?
我现在不就在吗
I'm here now.
现在不方便
Now is not a good time.
我有重要事情要跟你说
And I have something important to tell you.
别啊  现在别说
Don't tell him. Not now.
是什么
What is it?
-不  你醉了  -我就喝了两瓶啤酒
- No. You're drunk. - I had two beers.
说吧  给我个提示
Come on, give me, give me a hint.
这个...
Well...
我最近想了很多我们的事
I have been doing a lot of thinking about us,
我意识到了什么
and I realized something.
你要跟我分手吗
Are you breaking up with me?
天  不是
God, no.
好的
Okay.
我爱上你了
I'm in love with you.
我就是想知道
I just... I just thought it would be nice to know
你对我的感觉
how you felt about me.
我不会离开我妻子的
I'm not leaving my wife.
不  我不是叫你离开她
Yeah, no, I'm not asking you to.
我觉得就是
See, I think you are.
我觉得你喝多了  现在不太适合谈这个
I think you're too drunk to have this conversation.
你用了"爱"这词后
When you start using the "L word,"
男人可以很快清醒过来
a guy can sober up pretty quick.
你不爱我吗
You don't love me?
我觉得你很好
I think you're great.
你觉得我很好
You think I'm great?
这就是你的回复
That's your response?
你知道规则的  我当初说得很明白
You knew the rules. I was very clear.
我永远不会离开我妻子
I will never leave my wife!
-请别吼我  -你让我生气了
- Please don't yell at me. - Well, you're making me angry!
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
我
I-I...
那...
So...
我怎么办
where does that leave me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想你该走了
I think that you should go.
你还好吗
You okay?
嗯  他一般不这么跟我说话的
Yeah, he usually doesn't speak to me that way.
通常情况下他人都挺好的
He's normally very kind.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
我希望他妻子能意识到她有多幸运
Well, I hope his wife appreciates how lucky she is.
我可不确定她有这么幸运
I'm not sure she's that lucky.
所以...
So...
汤米·哈特
Tommy Harte.
我知道他有点小
I know he's a bit young...
只是有点吗  我第一次见他的时候  他才8岁
A bit? When I met him, he was eight.
你那时还是直男呢
And you were heterosexual.
现在这小屁孩成了你情人了
And now this child is your lover?
谁曾想到通奸和日托
Who knew there was such a fine line
差别这么小
between adultery and day care?
你滚  卡尔  你没资格评判我
Bugger off, Karl. You have no right to judge me.
我没有评判你
I'm not judging you,
我只是在戏弄你
I'm just teasing.
要说有什么的话  我为我们感到开心  喝酒吗
If anything, I'm happy for us. Drink?
白兰地  什么叫你为我们感到开心
Brandy. What do you mean you're happy for us?
你不明白吗  我们不需要离婚
Well, don't you see? We don't need to get a divorce.
我们无意中卷入了这完美的安排
We have stumbled into the perfect arrangement.
你有你的情人  我也有我的
You will have your lovers and I will have mine,
然后我们回家八卦我们的情事
and then we will come home to sparkling conversation.
这很欧洲
It's very European.
你不介意我和别人上床吗
It doesn't bother you that I'm having sex with someone else?
亲爱的  我是同性恋
Darling, I'm gay.
对我来说  和女人做爱就好比腾空洗碗机
Look, for me, sex with a woman is like emptying the dishwasher.
要是有人求我和女人做  我会的
I mean, I'll do it if I'm asked,
但如果有人自告奋勇  我也不会抱怨
but if someone else volunteers, I won't complain.
你知道我很喜欢这件衬衣的
Oh. You know I love this shirt.
你可以说你要喝伏特加啊
You might've asked for vodka.
我不懂  你怎么会不吃醋
I don't understand. How can you not be jealous?
抱歉  你想让我吃汤米·哈特的醋
Sorry, wait, you want me to be jealous of Tommy Harte?
他吃你的醋
He's jealous of you!
那是应该的  我是你老公
So he should be. I'm the husband.
不会太久了
Not for long.
你要怎么做  和我离婚再嫁给汤米吗
Oh, what are you gonna do, divorce me and marry Tommy?
-也许我会的  -很好  我会给你们准备礼物
- Maybe I will. - Oh, good. Well, I'll get you a gift.
你们什么时候去登记  费雪玩具要吗
Where will you be registered? Fisher-Price?
不是什么都是笑话的  卡尔
Everything is not a joke, Karl.
你这不是好笑  是冷酷
You're not being funny, you're being cruel.
亲爱的  我可不想冷酷无情  我爱你
Oh, darling, I'm not trying to be cruel. I love you.
不  你不爱
No, you don't!
不是我需要的那种爱
Not the way I need.
我想要一个深爱我的男人
I want a man who loves me so much
如果我和别人睡了  他会愿意去杀了那男人
that he would kill another man if I slept with someone else.
但是你永远做不到  对吗
And I'm never gonna get that from you, am I?
是的
No.
可你是我最好的朋友
But you're my best friend.
这不够
It's not enough.
该死
Shit.
喂  亲爱的
Yeah? Hey, babe.
怎么这么小声
Hey. Why are you whispering?
我在写作  你懂的
Oh, I was just, I was writing, so, you know...
我需要点时间才能从"脑海中的"声音
...takes me a minute to get out of the "In my head" Voice
回到我"大声说话的"声音
and back into the "Out loud" Voice.
-进展如何  -会议很顺利
- How did everything go? - Oh, the conference was great,
我的姐妹们还是老样子
and my sisters... are my sisters.
-嗯  -如果你在工作的话  我不想打扰你
- Yeah. - Look, if you're working, I don't want to stop you.
洁德醒着吗  我可以跟她聊
Um, is Jade up? I can talk to her.
她好像去遛狗了
I-I-I think she's walking the dog.
这个点去未免太晚了吧
It's a little late for that, no?
嗯  不过...
Yeah, but, you know...
狗可分不清时间
dog can't tell time, so...
我很高兴你打电话过来
I'm, uh... I'm glad you checked in.
当然  我爱你
Yeah. Um, I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.